The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal’s	I-COMPANY
War	O
on	O
Donald	B-PERSON
Trump	I-PERSON
https://t.co/mLbIxE6rbG	O

Everyone	O
Hates	O
Customer	O
Service.	O
This	O
Is	O
Why	O
|	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
via	O
/r/DailyTechNewsShow	O
https://t.co/1eK4LLlJSY	O
https://t.co/drPcnGkRD6	O

we	O
shouldnt	O
have	O
fair	O
elections	O
because	O
they	O
favor	O
democrats	O
—	O
wall	B-COMPANY
street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
editorial	O
board	O
https://t.co/U0y54fCmBv	O

"	O
Launching	O
a	O
Leadership	B-OTHER
Revolution	I-OTHER
"	O
-	O
NY	B-COMPANY
Times,	I-COMPANY
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
and	O
USA	B-COMPANY
Today	I-COMPANY
best	O
seller	O
#leadership	O
https://t.co/mhFIp3SIH9	O

Hong	B-GEO-LOC
Kong	I-GEO-LOC
Protesters	O
Battle	O
Police,	B-ORG
Despite	O
Beijing’s	B-GEO-LOC
Warnings	O
–	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/XSG3R4BX3J	O

#Turkey	B-GEO-LOC
plans	O
to	O
#relocate	O
700,000	O
Syrians	O
to	O
northern	O
#Syria	B-GEO-LOC
-	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
|	O
https://t.co/IEIermV1mG	O

Manchester	B-GEO-LOC
City	I-GEO-LOC
,	O
Liverpool	B-GEO-LOC
Widen	I-GEO-LOC
the	O
Premier	O
League	I-OTHER
Gap	I-OTHER
–	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/UbNQHsus1G	O
https://t.co/NcKiIJihpp	O

according	O
to	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
,	O
a	O
more	O
ironic	O
and	O
certainly	O
unlikely	O
beverage	O
brand	O
is	O
taking	O
a	O
leap	O
into	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
THC	O
and	O
CBD-infused	O
products	O
:	O
Arizona	B-COMPANY
Iced	I-COMPANY
Tea	I-COMPANY
.	O
Yes,	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
company	O
known	O
for	O
pushing	O
out	O
millions	O
of	O
brightly	O
colored	O
…	O
https://t.co/GAszjX9zNY	O
https://t.co/nstNMTJ1sd	O

Microsoft	B-COMPANY
Aims	O
to	O
Reset	O
Videogame	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
Streaming	I-OTHER
Market	O
With	O
‘	O
Ninja	O
’	O
Pact	O
–	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/uNecZMjQs7	O

I	O
defend	O
diversity	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
(click	O
photo	O
or	O
link)	O
The	B-COMPANY
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
@WSJ	O
https://t.co/GPvaMrdU5p	O
https://t.co/6uw3FRX7x1	O

Calling	O
rednecks	O
Nationalists	O
with	O
a	O
capitol	O
'N'	O
wallstreetjournal	B-COMPANY
Rednecks	O
r	O
violent	O
when	O
drunk	O
'	O
others	O
who	O
study'	O
you	O
dont	O
know	O
any	O
who	O
study	O
rednecks	O
apparently	O
WSJ	B-COMPANY
doesnt	O
know	O
WHAT	O
a	O
redneck	O
is	O
Ask	O
the	O
boys	O
from	O
Covington	B-GEO-LOC
Ky	I-GEO-LOC
.	O
What	O
is	O
a	O
redneck	O
|	O
every	O
hand	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
quickly	O

Take	O
an	O
early	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
The	B-COMPANY
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/5xQPDPcm8q	O
https://t.co/By1yuHeQ6e	O

New	O
Article:	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
BlackRock	B-COMPANY
set	O
to	O
take	O
major	O
stake	O
in	O
Sports	B-COMPANY
Illustrated	I-COMPANY
owner	O
Authentic	B-COMPANY
Brands	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/tqUhbbPktY	O
#WallSt	O
August	O
11,	O
2019	O

Brilliant	O
semiotic	O
musings	O
on	O
student	O
debt	O
and	O
more	O
➡️	O
#Repost	O
@davidplunkert	O
・・・	O
Cover	O
Art	O
for	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
St.	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
"	O
The	O
Long	O
Road	O
to	O
the	O
College	O
Debt	O
Crisis	O
"	O
#wallstreetjournal	B-COMPANY
#art	O
direction	O
#collegedebt	O
#davidplunkert	O
#editorialillustration	O
#stu…	O
https://t.co/Fb1QRqWCdw	O
https://t.co/s6O3GUXPVS	O

A	O
Social-Media	O
Guide	O
for	O
Introverts	O
-	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/mThiVhqMNP	O
https://t.co/2k7FTAUrhp	O

Hong	B-GEO-LOC
Kong’s	I-GEO-LOC
Protesters	O
Test	O
Riot	O
Police	B-ORG
With	O
Cat-and-Mouse	O
Tactics	O
–	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/be4w9S4cwg	O

@CBurbaugh	O
@alamnavsa	O
@sgsfilms	O
@ladylawyerpam	O
@BrunoAmato_1	O
@GOPChairwoman	O
@realDonaldTrump	O
From	O
that	O
bastion	O
of	O
liberalism	O
,	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
https://t.co/QrbrqtSbRD	O

California	B-GEO-LOC
Fostered	O
America’s	O
Tech	O
Industry	O
.	O
It	O
Is	O
Becoming	O
a	O
Great	O
Adversary	O
.	O
-	O
The	B-OTHER
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/UReAYhbPdn	O
#CCPA	O
https://t.co/AcRb4aKhmC	O

@EddieDonovan	B-PERSON
OMG,	O
they	O
even	O
show	O
pictures	O
of	O
bodies	O
being	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
morgue	O
!	O
OANN	B-ORG
deserves	O
to	O
be	O
sued.	O
Peter	B-PERSON
Smith	I-PERSON
"	O
died	O
"	O
after	O
an	O
interview	O
with	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal,	I-OTHER
owned	O
by	O
Rupert	B-PERSON
Murdoch	I-PERSON
.	O

Russian	B-ORG
Nuclear	I-ORG
Agency	I-ORG
Confirms	O
Deaths	O
During	O
Engine	O
Test	O
–	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/J2MH9i9ilE	O

Russia	B-GEO-LOC
Protests	O
Present	O
New	O
Challenge	O
to	O
Putin	B-PERSON
’s	O
Dominance	O
–	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/MbC8Ba0bAN	O
https://t.co/nS8LdI7cIH	O

Highly	O
thought	O
-	O
(	O
provoking	O
article	O
!	O
Great	O
job	O
by	O
#reporter	O
@joshmitchell24	O
at	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
@WSJ_Online	O
https://t.co/NqjhXzF7S4	O

Sahara	B-PERSON
:	O
For	O
the	O
United	B-GEO-LOC
States	I-GEO-LOC
,	O
independence	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
option	O
(	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
)	O
https://t.co/NtEcYy0wGi	O
https://t.co/lZZsOAXlnX	O

Millionaires	O
deny	O
the	O
ban	O
of	O
religion	O
at	O
Kinaluatic	B-GEO-LOC
Island	I-GEO-LOC
-	O
information	O
from	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/sMBI7ZvZrw	O

Greenspan	B-PERSON
doubled	O
down	O
on	O
an	O
opinion	O
piece	O
he	O
and	O
fellow	O
former	O
Fed	O
Chairs	O
Paul	B-PERSON
Volker	I-PERSON
,	O
Ben	B-PERSON
Bernanke	I-PERSON
,	O
and	O
Janet	B-PERSON
Yellen	I-PERSON
wrote	O
last	O
week	O
for	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal,	I-OTHER
in	O
which	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
an	O
independent	O
Federal	B-ORG
Reserve	I-ORG
.	O
He	O
said,	O
Politics	O
does	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
enter	O
into	O
this	O
.	O
https://t.co/ZChZkwDv31	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-GEO-LOC
Journal	I-COMPANY
on	O
Uber	B-COMPANY
/	O
Lyft	B-COMPANY
bailout	O
request	O
from	O
CA	B-ORG
Legislature	O
for	O
low	O
-	O
road	O
business	O
model	O
.	O

“	O
Uber	B-COMPANY
/	O
Lyft	B-COMPANY
...	O
would	O
face	O
a	O
direct	O
threat	O
to	O
their	O
business	O
model	O
if	O
it	O
(	O
#AB5	O
)	O
passes	O
.	O
The	O
companies	O
are	O
unprofitable	O
even	O
w	O
/	O
labor	O
costs	O
at	O
current	O
levels	O
.	O
”	O
https://t.co/GTaJ0WsQUg	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
/	O
Times	B-ORG
Higher	I-ORG
Education	I-ORG
College	I-ORG
Rankings	O
#5-Top	O
Schools	O
for	O
Career	O
Preparation	O
#Number1Engineering	O
#CareerU	O
https://t.co/hHrlT7KsP4	O

Cate	O
para	O
o	O
WSJ	B-COMPANY
(	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
)	O
,	O
por	O
Ian	B-PERSON
Patterson	I-PERSON
.	O
https://t.co/UuwqWzGVbF	O

are	O
proud	O
to	O
host	O
@MrAndyNgo	B-OTHER
for	O
an	O
IRL	B-EVE
speaking	I-EVE
event	O
!	O
Andy	B-PERSON
writes	O
for	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
,	O
New	B-COMPANY
York	I-COMPANY
Post	I-COMPANY
,	O
and	O
National	B-COMPANY
Review	I-COMPANY
to	O
name	O
a	O
few	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
also	O
an	O
editor	O
for	O
@Quillette	O
Use	O
code	O
ANDY	O
to	O
save	O
10%	O
on	O
tickets:	O
https://t.co/yW8KpGHDad	O
Sat.	O
August	O
31	O
NJ	O
#MINDS	O
IRL	O
https://t.co/jlKpPrEAPb	O

#CSUEB	O
students,	O
faculty	O
and	O
staff	O
can	O
read	O
the	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
for	O
free	O
!	O
Details	O
👇	O
https://t.co/hDglEjuU2u	O

WSJ	B-COMPANY
Report:	O
New	O
Nintendo	B-PRODUCT
Switch	I-PRODUCT
Hardware	O
Getting	O
Bleeding	O
Edge	O
Sharp	O
IGZO	O
Display	O
!	O

Watch	O
My	O
New	O
Video	O
Here	O
:	O
https://t.co/nzpZIYxVf4	O
#NintendoSwitch	O
#SharpIGZO	O
#wallstreetjournal	O
https://t.co/5b2cKYMiiv	O

It	O
was	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
today	O
when	O
the	O
official	O
@Parkeology	O
#parkeologychallenge	O
was	O
featured	O
on	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
community	O
of	O
people	O
who	O
have	O
formed	O
around	O
the	O
Parkeology	B-OTHER
Challenge	I-OTHER
and	O
the	O
friendships	O
we	O
have	O
made	O
.	O
Thanks!	O
https://t.co/NV3d75nLTg	O

Come	O
speak	O
with	O
Sara	B-PERSON
Radil	I-PERSON
is	O
the	O
assistant	O
managing	O
editor	O
at	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
She	O
is	O
excited	O
for	O
the	O
partnership	O
reception	O
to	O
night	O
with	O
Morgan	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
.	O
#NABJ19	O
@SGJCMSU	O
https://t.co/TAX7FtWz5M	O

DO	O
NO	O
HARM	O
is	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
limited	O
collection	O
of	O
medical	O
thrillers	O
written	O
by	O
USA	B-COMPANY
Today	I-COMPANY
,	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	O
and	O
Amazon	B-COMPANY
best	O
-	O
selling	O
authors	O
.	O
PREORDER	O
NOW	O
FOR	O
ONLY	O
99	O
CENTS	O
https://t.co/PgQ9LSvtKF	O
#medicalthriller	O
#medicalthriller	O
https://t.co/FIjXHy3Qvw	O

The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
says	O
the	O
millions	O
trial	O
against	O
Katy	B-PERSON
Perry	I-PERSON
has	O
had	O
records	O
of	O
companies	O
worried	O
about	O
a	O
breach	O
attack	O
.	O

“	O
Lawyers	O
,	O
musicologists	O
and	O
songwriters	O
say	O
these	O
cases	O
unfairly	O
punish	O
artists	O
for	O
using	O
common	O
musical	O
elements	O
.	O
”	O
https://t.co/nny92Klpga	O

#Libya	B-GEO-LOC
06.08.19	O
-	O
"	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
"	O
team	O
reporting	O
on	O
#migrants	O
crisis	O
from	O
Tajoura	B-GEO-LOC
ImmDC	O
#Migrantcrisis	O
#UNHCR	O
#LibyanCoastGuard	O
#LibyscheKüstenwache	O
#Seenotrettung	O
#BackAtSea	O
#Frontex	O
#Europol	O
#AlanKurdi	O
#HumanSmuggling	O
#EKD	O
#EU	O
https://t.co/CnsbPCQlum	O

Here	O
's	O
an	O
early	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
's	O
weekend	O
edition	O
https://t.co/rl8DV3Oq9C	O
https://t.co/PgdZIsatke	O

.	O
@DaleJr	O
'	O
nerds	O
out	O
on	O
cycling	O
data	O
,	O
’	O
70s-era	O
autos	O
and	O
steering	O
in	O
VR	O
,	O
'	O
he	O
tells	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
's	O
Technology	O
Essentials	O
feature	O
:	O
-	O
https://t.co/Zhj6cSAIU0	O
https://t.co/mrAmtseYgV	O

Find	O
from	O
the	O
Armstrong	B-PERSON
locker	O
removal	O
:	O
April	O
1957	O
issue	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/3MkJh0WWZ3	O

GROUND	O
ZERO	O
come	O
up	O
at	O
4pm	O
today	O
on	O
Invicta	O
98.9fm.	O
SNIPPETS	O
1	B-PERSON
-	I-PERSON
Sowore	I-PERSON
and	O
Dadiyata	B-PERSON
abducted	O
by	O
unknown	O
persons	O
.	O
...	O
As	O
Nigerians	O
call	O
for	O
their	O
release	O
2	O
-	O
Followingnthe	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
reports	O
the	O
Nigerian	B-ORG
Army	I-ORG
Denies	O
Existence	O
Of	O
Secret	O
Graveyard	O
Where	O
1000	O
Soldiers	O
Buried	O
https://t.co/tzPkqxw9it	O

It	O
's	O
US	O
publication	O
day	O
of	O
The	O
Intelligence	O
Trap	O
!	O
And	O
it	O
couldn't	O
have	O
started	O
better	O
than	O
finding	O
copies	O
in	O
Barnes	B-COMPANY
And	I-COMPANY
Noble	I-COMPANY
on	O
5th	O
Avenue	O
and	O
finding	O
a	O
review	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/s5bHWYLl7l	O
https://t.co/rOQU8hYoIv	O

My	O
arms	O
are	O
sore	O
from	O
pinching	O
myself	O
...	O
this	O
wkend's	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
features	O
my	O
I	O
Know	O
What	O
I	O
Saw	O
in	O
book	O
reviews	O
.	O
Many	O
Thanks	O
Tom	B-PERSON
Shippey	I-PERSON
&amp;	O
shoutout	O
for	O
starting	O
with	O
your	O
own	O
example	O
!	O
Loved	O
it	O
!	O
https://t.co/PPbZlc6Bvw	O

Is	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
separating	O
itself	O
from	O
the	O
faltering	O
White	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
?	O
Is	O
Navarro	B-PERSON
creating	O
division	O
between	O
Trump	B-PERSON
and	O
the	O
Murdoch	B-PERSON
owned	O
paper	O
?	O
Are	O
the	O
Murdoch	B-PERSON
s	I-PERSON
attempting	O
to	O
save	O
what's	O
left	O
of	O
their	O
reputations	O
?	O
Rats	O
are	O
jumping	O
ship	O
.	O
https://t.co/jHiP2Viv8w	O

#WillametteUniversity	B-ORG
is	O
ranked	O
#8	O
in	O
the	O
nation	O
for	O
best	O
student	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
staff	I-OTHER
interaction	O
by	O
the	O
Times	B-COMPANY
Higher	I-COMPANY
Education	I-COMPANY
/	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
Kudos	O
to	O
our	O
fantastic	O
faculty	O
members	O
!	O
https://t.co/k8Kx037kg6	O
#WillametteU	O
#WUAdmit	O
@wuadmit	O
@WillametteAlum	O
@CTCLColleges	O
@OregonAlliance	O
https://t.co/ZxpIbSFlLU	O

Trump	B-PERSON
talks	O
about	O
economics	O
like	O
someone	O
who	O
just	O
scanned	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
and	O
is	O
trying	O
to	O
bullshit	O
their	O
way	O
through	O
an	O
intermediate	O
macro	O
or	O
money	O
and	O
banking	O
course	O
.	O
@menzie_chinn	O
https://t.co/7U9NchPmEL	O

Why	O
did	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	B-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
piece	O
on	O
whether	O
bankers	O
can	O
wear	O
shorts	O
to	O
work	O
during	O
a	O
heatwave	O
.	O
https://t.co/wYjN3xFrbE	O

According	O
to	O
a	O
report	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
dramatic	O
rise	O
in	O
snakebites	O
across	O
US	B-GEO-LOC
and	O
it's	O
linked	O
to	O
the	O
#climatecrisis	O
...	O

North	B-GEO-LOC
Carolina	I-GEO-LOC
,	O
Georgia	B-GEO-LOC
and	O
Texas	B-GEO-LOC
on	O
track	O
to	O
break	O
records	O
#ClimateChangeIsReal	O
#ClimateActionNow	O
https://t.co/x8rceYGI1S	O
https://t.co/FnsazS15bo	O

The	O
right	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
wing	I-OTHER
media	O
has	O
been	O
trying	O
to	O
turn	O
former	O
Google	B-COMPANY
engineer	O
Kevin	B-PERSON
Cernekee,	I-PERSON
who	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
fired	O
for	O
being	O
conservative	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
poster	O
boy	O
for	O
their	O
claim	O
that	O
big	O
tech	O
is	O
anti	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
conservative	I-OTHER
.	O
This	O
started	O
with	O
a	O
big	O
profile	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
https://t.co/47RsWj7QT0	O

https://t.co/gu727PXmeq	O
Jason	B-PERSON
Zweig	I-PERSON
’s	O
latest	O
#investigative	O
#journalism	O
piece	O
was	O
published	O
in	O
the	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
last	O
week	O
,	O
J.R.	B-PERSON
Robinson	I-PERSON
helped	O
with	O
the	O
piece	O

In	O
the	O
Family	O
:	O
Graydon	B-PERSON
Carter	I-PERSON
’s	O
1951	O
#Chevrolet	B-COMPANY
|	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
|	O
https://t.co/MGInDm0zmd	O

During	O
the	O
25	O
years	O
he	O
edited	O
Vanity	B-OTHER
Fair	I-OTHER
this	O
vintage	O
woodie	O
was	O
the	O
car	O
for	O
weekend	O
getaways	O
!	O
#ThrowbackThursday	O
https://t.co/2zXmf3B9Cp	O

GIVEAWAY	O
-	O
From	O
the	O
Amazon	B-OTHER
Charts	I-OTHER
and	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
bestselling	O
author	O
of	O
the	O
Everything	O
series	O
,	O
@kerrylonsdale	B-PERSON
comes	O
a	O
new	O
novel	O
of	O
love	O
,	O
lies	O
,	O
and	O
deceit	O
.	O
THE	O
LAST	O
SUMMER	O
(	O
@LUAuthors	O
)	O
will	O
have	O
you	O
hooked	O
from	O
page	O
one	O
.	O
https://t.co/hjKInwgiQ9	O
@TLCBookTours	O
https://t.co/XNpzIjqVxe	O

#DidYouKnow	O
CBE	B-COMPANY
has	O
partnered	O
with	O
@WSJ	B-COMPANY
to	O
give	O
FREE	O
SUBSCRIPTIONS	O
to	O
ALL	O
students	O
,	O
faculty	O
,	O
and	O
staff	O
in	O
the	O
university	O
?	O
Use	O
your	O
NetID	O
to	O
sign	O
in	O
at	O
https://t.co/Yc66zJhDQV	O
to	O
get	O
desktop	O
and	O
mobile	O
access	O
.	O
#CSUEBCBE	O
@CalStateEastBay	O
#CSUEB	O
#CalStateEastBay	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
https://t.co/WLBxAGueTi	O

Take	O
an	O
early	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/5xQPDPcm8q	O
https://t.co/L3r9DKmRPp	O

President	O
Kenny	B-PERSON
Vieth	I-PERSON
quoted	O
in	O
The	O
Wall	B-OTHER
Street	I-OTHER
Journal	I-OTHER
Logistics	I-OTHER
report	O
again	O
today	O
discussing	O
#freight	O
.	O
https://t.co/Lway9hr4FS	O

A	O
new	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
portrait	O
.	O
Here's	O
an	O
illustration	O
of	O
Caroline	B-PERSON
Glover	I-PERSON
,	O
founder	O
and	O
chef	O
of	O
Annette	B-COMPANY
in	O
Aurora	B-GEO-LOC
,	I-GEO-LOC
Colorado	I-GEO-LOC
,	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Off	O
Duty	O
section	O
of	O
this	O
past	O
weekends'	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
Thanks	O
to	O
my	O
wondrous	O
AD	O
,	O
@ufoundforest!	O
https://t.co/SE9CzFsgBY	O

If	O
I	O
can't	O
answer	O
39	O
Down	O
,	O
there's	O
a	O
problem	O
.	O
#familyties	O
#ushistory	O
#wallstreetjournal	O
#wsj	B-COMPANY
#crossword	O
https://t.co/3kC6USJe6a	O

Oil	O
and	O
gas	O
companies	O
are	O
scrambling	O
to	O
reduce	O
methane	O
emissions	O
—	O
both	O
unintended	O
and	O
deliberate	O
—	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
U.S.	B-GEO-LOC
alone	O
equate	O
to	O
the	O
exhaust	O
from	O
69	O
million	O
cars	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
contribute	O
to	O
global	B-EVE
warming	I-EVE
https://t.co/3tyLqOTvw1	O

Sarah	B-PERSON
Rabil	I-PERSON
is	O
the	O
Assistant	O
Managing	O
Editor	O
at	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
She	O
shares	O
her	O
experience	O
with	O
me	O
thus	O
far	O
at	O
the	O
NABJ	B-EVE
conference	I-EVE
.	O
She’s	O
excited	O
for	O
our	O
joint	O
reception	O
with	O
Morgan	B-PERSON
tonight	O
!	O
@srabil	O
#SGJCNABJ	O
https://t.co/wK7hbFx1zb	O

The	O
White	B-OTHER
House	I-OTHER
is	O
now	O
at	O
odds	O
with	O
Fox	B-TVSHOW
News	I-TVSHOW
anchors	O
on	O
racist	O
rhetoric	O
,	O
the	O
New	B-COMPANY
York	I-COMPANY
Post	I-COMPANY
on	O
assault	O
weapons	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
on	O
economic	O
policy	O
.	O

According	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
the	O
#NintendoSwitch	B-PRODUCT
may	O
be	O
getting	O
another	O
upgrade	O
!	O
https://t.co/1jQcQyDaoa	O
https://t.co/jhHW7ILxBs	O

By	O
me	O
:	O
“	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
has	O
unfortunately	O
amplified	O
the	O
myth	O
that	O
social	O
media	O
is	O
censoring	O
conservatives	O
”	O
https://t.co/wbgOCZh2kA	O

what	O
exactly	O
is	O
the	O
problem	O
here	O
wall	B-COMPANY
street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/5Dm1BIsWUr	O

Quantum	B-COMPANY
Technology	I-COMPANY
Captures	O
Headlines	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/TMa0RwM43F	O
by	O
@cloudsa	O

It’s	O
not	O
everyday	O
that	O
a	B-OTHER
country	I-OTHER
gal	I-OTHER
finds	O
herself	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O

I’m	O
happy	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
#methane	O
leaks	O
and	O
intentional	O
venting	O
receive	O
this	O
level	O
of	O
exposure	O
.	O

The	O
graphics	O
tho’	O
.	O
💕	O
#ClimateCrisis	O
https://t.co/ORceIAQOzA	O

Washington	B-GEO-LOC
State	I-GEO-LOC
has	O
the	O
#1	O
economy	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
and	O
the	O
#3	O
most	O
unionized	O
work	O
force	O
.	O

Major	O
Wall	B-OTHER
Street	I-OTHER
banks	I-OTHER
hand	O
over	O
treasure	O
trove	O
of	O
information	O
on	O
Russians	O
linked	O
to	O
Trump	B-PERSON
and	O
family	O
:	O
report	O
#Russia	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
#DonaldTrump	B-PERSON
https://t.co/JfgUl8ItMy	O
https://t.co/X1NDKJDLzl	O

Take	O
an	O
early	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/M1GpXqmm8k	O
https://t.co/Dd9yXJovch	O

The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
Fox	B-COMPANY
Corp.	I-COMPANY
to	O
buy	O
majority	O
stake	O
in	O
Credible	B-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
for	O
$265	O
million	O
https://t.co/oiUJIbNWMp	O
#people	O
#money	O
https://t.co/FRfAasHTGs	O

"	O
When	O
your	O
face	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
,	O
you	O
make	O
sure	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
copy	O
.	O
Came	O
in	O
the	O
mail	O
today	O
"	O
Credits	O
to	O
Jenna	B-PERSON
Zito	I-PERSON
Clark	I-PERSON
#RandyHarrison	B-PERSON
#Cabaret	O
#Emcee	O
https://t.co/YyrAZwtcXk	O

this	O
is	O
definitely	O
my	O
maw	O
maw’s	O
first	O
appearance	O
in	O
the	O
wall	B-COMPANY
street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY

Alleged	O
Chinese	B-OTHER
Bllionaire	I-OTHER
Spy	I-OTHER
Guo	B-PERSON
Wengui	I-PERSON
fired	O
lawsuits	O
against	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
@WSJ	B-COMPANY
CNN	B-COMPANY
@CNN	B-COMPANY
Miami	B-COMPANY
Herald	I-COMPANY
@MiamiHerald	B-COMPANY
CBS12	B-COMPANY
@CBS12	B-COMPANY

Who	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
？	O
@BBCWorld	B-COMPANY
@nytimesworld	B-COMPANY
@washingtonpost	B-COMPANY
@politico	O
https://t.co/MFmZv9AduT	O

@pjmorton	B-MUSICARTIST
new	O
album	O
“	O
Paul	O
”	O
out	O
this	O
Friday	O
.	O
Proud	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
......	O
look	O
Mommy	O
my	O
picture	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
#wallstreetjournal	B-COMPANY
🙂	O
https://t.co/jhOBM89bwL	O

@ThusuVanshita	B-PERSON
@SushmaSwaraj	B-PERSON
@SushmaSwaraj	B-PERSON
,	O
India's	O
"	O
best	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
loved	I-OTHER
politician	O
"	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
US	B-ORG
daily	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
May	O
her	O
soul	O
rest	O
in	O
peace🙏🏻	O
https://t.co/ZdVoDo8xkA	O

We	O
are	O
only	O
6	O
days	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
pre	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
order	I-OTHER
day	O
!	O

On	O
Aug	O
.	O
14th	O
,	O
the	O
book	O
collection	O
goes	O
up	O
to	O
$9.99	O
!	O
Order	O
today	O
for	O
only	O
$0.99	O
A	O
wild	O
west	O
thrill	O
ride	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
USA	B-COMPANY
Today	I-COMPANY
,	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
and	O
Amazon	B-COMPANY
best	I-COMPANY
-	I-COMPANY
selling	I-COMPANY
and	O
award-winning	O
authors	O
.	O
Proceeds	O
to	O
AWHC	O
https://t.co/7VF5xLbaEl	O

Tucker	B-PERSON
Carlson	I-PERSON
:	O
White	O
supremacy	O
is	O
"	O
actually	O
not	O
a	O
real	O
problem	O
in	O
America	B-GEO-LOC
.	O
"	O
Calling	O
white	O
supremacy	O
and	O
issue	O
is	O
"	O
a	O
hoax	O
"	O
and	O
"	O
a	O
conspiracy	O
theory	O
used	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
country	O
"	O
https://t.co/ydzmJ0L7UI	O

WALL	B-COMPANY
STREET	I-COMPANY
JOURNAL	I-COMPANY
:	O
“	O
The	O
use	O
of	O
drugs	O
as	O
a	O
quick	O
fix	O
doesn’t	O
help	O
kids	O
become	O
resilient	O
to	O
stress	O
or	O
emotionally	O
mature	O
.	O
The	O
use	O
of	O
psychiatric	O
drugs	O
to	O
treat	O
ADHD	O
,	O
depression	O
and	O
anxiety	O
in	O
children	O
and	O
teens	O
has	O
been	O
increasing	O
and	O
is	O
excessive	O
.	O
”	O
https://t.co/FNcvAkVoSc	O

"	O
Push	B-OTHER
notifications	I-OTHER
past	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
"	O
by	O
@wsj	B-COMPANY
https://t.co/PK2zkPI0Hp	O
#wsj	B-COMPANY
#wallstreetjournal	B-COMPANY

From	O
that	O
commie	O
rag	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
https://t.co/mjInyEdYZs	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
highlights	O
#Kashmir	O
#SOSKashmir	O
https://t.co/DSAI0gJ8Qr	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
•	O
front	O
page	O
•	O
August	O
7	O
2019	O
https://t.co/VmPkZ5QFa0	O
https://t.co/ek73MrJbpS	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
If	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
better	O
at	O
marathoning	O
spend	O
tons	O
of	O
$$	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
1%	O
of	O
performance	O
.	O

Real	O
Life	O
:	O
If	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
better	O
at	O
marathoning	O
run	O
often	O
—	O
some	O
days	O
hard	O
,	O
some	O
days	O
easy	O
;	O
sleep	O
8	O
hrs	O
;	O
eat	O
whole	O
foods	O
;	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
friends	O
.	O
https://t.co/9htJn4dZ8S	O

Sensitive	B-OTHER
digital	I-OTHER
data	I-OTHER
can	O
already	O
be	O
recorded	O
today	O
and	O
#decrypted	O
once	O
a	O
powerful	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
enough	I-OTHER
#QuantumComputer	B-PRODUCT
is	O
available	O
...	O
https://t.co/pYTzSEC71G	O

Nigeria	B-GEO-LOC
:	O
PDP	B-ORG
challenges	O
National	B-ORG
Assembly	I-ORG
to	O
probe	O
alleged	O
secret	O
burial	O
of	O
1000	O
soldiers	O
#allegedsecretburialof1000soldiers	O
#PDP	B-ORG
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
https://t.co/gBkKBg1FXh	O
https://t.co/HvpqZpT9Kg	O

Take	O
a	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
today's	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/fIBlOXnf3u	O
https://t.co/k21usykDdA	O

Oh	O
my	O
god	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
shUT	O
UUUUPPPP	O
https://t.co/QXA3cbPYrA	O

In	O
1997	O
,	O
Tucker	B-PERSON
Carlson	I-PERSON
was	O
writing	O
for	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
...	O
warning	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
white	O
nationalist	O
John	B-ORG
Tanton	I-ORG
organization	I-ORG
's	O
infiltration	O
of	O
the	O
environmental	O
movement	O
.	O

It	O
wasn't	O
a	O
hoax	O
then	O
...	O
#FireTuckerCarlson	O
https://t.co/lmsIbyuFne	O

Heads	O
up	O
American	B-OTHER
business	I-OTHER
owners	I-OTHER
!	O
Your	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Oval	B-ORG
Office	I-ORG
can’t	O
pay	O
on	O
time	O
for	O
his	O
2020	O
campaign	O
!	O
Now	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
is	O
calling	O
him	O
an	O
urgent	O
threat	O
.	O
#GOP	O
#SenateRepublicans	O
The	O
blood	O
is	O
on	O
your	O
hands	O
.	O
https://t.co/HKYpZ2jzaE	O
https://t.co/efIbNR2Ft1	O

From	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
...	O
see	O
below	O
https://t.co/mHsEZhfuR7	O

This	O
bait	O
and	O
switch	O
isn't	O
surprising	O
coming	O
from	O
Dennis	B-PERSON
"	O
There's	O
No	O
Such	O
Thing	O
as	O
White	O
Nationalism	O
"	O
Prager	B-PERSON
,	O
but	O
it	O
IS	O
shocking	O
that	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
can	O
no	O
longer	O
be	O
bothered	O
to	O
distinguish	O
actual	O
Nazis	O
from	O
conservatives	O
when	O
it's	O
convenient	O
to	O
blur	O
that	O
vital	O
line	O
https://t.co/NDsRAUVVMu	O

The	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
|	O
Trump	B-PERSON
is	O
struggling	O
to	O
crank	O
up	O
his	O
promised	O
...	O
#BarackObama	B-PERSON
#TheWallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
https://t.co/j9fcD0qwJw	O
https://t.co/PTpEhRsRL5	O

#Blockchain	O
Marks	O
the	O
Next	O
Step	O
in	O
the	O
Internet’s	O
Evolution	O
-	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/U6YmqK9cJH	O
#Tech	O
https://t.co/ooMi9Z5UDH	O

"	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
The	O
Fasting	O
Cure	O
Is	O
No	O
Fad	O
"	O
via	O
@FastingLane	O
https://t.co/By0MkEV9w9	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
If	O
You	O
Want	O
‘	O
#Renewable	B-OTHER
Energy	I-OTHER
,	O
’	O
Get	O
Ready	O
to	O
Dig	O
https://t.co/bvXH2qwmDM	O
"	O
World	O
demand	O
for	O
#RareEarths	B-OTHER
elements	I-OTHER
—	O
which	O
aren’t	O
rare	O
but	O
are	O
rarely	O
mined	O
in	O
America	O
—	O
will	O
rise	O
300%	O
to	O
1,000%	O
by	O
2050	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Paris	B-EVE
green	I-EVE
goals	I-EVE
.	O
"	O
https://t.co/vbQQik9Sf4	O

every	O
time	O
i	O
get	O
a	O
notification	O
from	O
the	O
wall	B-COMPANY
street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
opinion	O
section	O
i	O
feel	O
the	O
sudden	O
urge	O
to	O
throw	O
myself	O
off	O
a	O
bridge	O
https://t.co/XgjcqeuxWC	O

Not	O
many	O
political	O
leaders	O
achieve	O
success	O
in	O
winning	O
hearts	O
of	O
people	O
even	O
from	O
the	O
opposition	O
.	O
Had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
finest	O
political	O
careers	O
and	O
an	O
excellent	O
orator	O
and	O
human	O
being	O
.	O
Rightly	O
described	O
by	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
as	O
India's	B-OTHER
Best	I-OTHER
Loved	I-OTHER
Politician	I-OTHER
.	O
RIP	O
#sushmaswaraj	B-PERSON
ji	O
🙏	O

A	O
small	O
way	O
that	O
the	O
president	O
can	O
help	O
#ElPaso	B-GEO-LOC
—	O
he	O
could	O
pay	O
his	O
bill	O
to	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
now	O
up	O
to	O
$569,204.63.	O
https://t.co/zpaeh7eovb	O
by	O
@davelevinthal	B-PERSON
@publicintegrity	O
https://t.co/mV4n5He5dz	O

Chinese	B-ORG
Troops	I-ORG
in	O
Hong	B-GEO-LOC
Kong	I-GEO-LOC
Keep	O
Low	O
Profile	O
but	O
Stand	O
Ready	O
–	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/I2tMxke4lT	O
https://t.co/AJgWuZa3Mm	O

This	O
week	O
on	O
Cultured	O
,	O
I	O
talk	O
all	O
things	O
#FastandFuriousHobbsandShaw	O
,	O
including	O
that	O
bizarre	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
report	O
about	O
its	O
stars	O
and	O
their	O
contracts	O
.	O

Listen	O
here	O
:	O
https://t.co/WRvFWmbxBE	O
https://t.co/kvOkSoDpWI	O

Another	O
huge	O
THANKS	O
to	O
my	O
awesome	O
readers	O
!	O
#6	O
on	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
bestseller	B-OTHER
list	I-OTHER
!!!!	O
https://t.co/2qq4joUylV	O

GROUND	B-GEO-LOC
ZERO	I-GEO-LOC
come	O
up	O
at	O
4pm	O
today	O
on	O
Invicta	O
98.9fm.	O
SNIPPETS	O
1-	O
Sowore	B-PERSON
and	O
Dadiyata	B-PERSON
abducted	O
by	O
unknown	O
persons	O
.	O
...As	O
Nigerians	O
call	O
for	O
their	O
release	O
2-	O
Followingnthe	B-OTHER
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
reports	O
the	O
Nigerian	B-ORG
Army	I-ORG
Denies	O
Existence	O
Of	O
Secret	O
Graveyard	O
Where	O
1000	O
Soldiers	O
Buried	O
https://t.co/3vi1zksQPX	O

Take	O
an	O
early	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
The	B-COMPANY
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/tYCeELTJqc	O
https://t.co/aS4eIHAmvy	O

I	O
felt	O
like	O
WEEPING	O
after	O
reading	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
’s	O
story	O
of	O
how	O
General	B-PERSON
@MBuhari	I-PERSON
covered	O
up	O
the	O
killing	O
of	O
1000	O
troops	O
by	O
Boko	B-ORG
Haram	I-ORG
in	O
the	O
last	O
one	O
year	O
by	O
burying	O
them	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
And	O
2	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
Buhari	B-PERSON
said	O
he	O
has	O
'	O
defeated	O
'	O
Boko	B-ORG
Haram	I-ORG
!	O
#GeneralBuhariSecretlyBuriesSoldiers	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
slaps	O
Trump	B-COMPANY
for	O
latest	O
stock	O
market	O
crippling	O
tariffs	O
that	O
will	O
hurt	O
‘	O
innocent	O
economic	O
bystanders	O
’	O
https://t.co/shJNJcB9xG	O
https://t.co/HreiiXCDDQ	O

#Aftermath	O
now	O
a	O
National	B-OTHER
Bestseller	I-OTHER
and	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
Bestseller	I-COMPANY
,	O
#4	O
on	O
hardcover	O
business	O
list	O
:	O
https://t.co/byU1OaoQCr.	O
Thanks	O
for	O
your	O
support	O
!	O
Book	B-PRODUCT
available	O
here:	O
https://t.co/kGeuucCJfl	O

@NateSilver538	B-PERSON
Never	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
NY	B-COMPANY
Post	I-COMPANY
and	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
would	O
be	O
more	O
critical	O
of	O
Trump	B-PERSON
then	O
the	O
NYT	B-COMPANY

Rupert	B-PERSON
Murdoch	I-PERSON
's	O
News	B-COMPANY
Corp	I-COMPANY
media	O
empire	O
has	O
for	O
decades	O
been	O
a	O
source	O
of	O
gross	O
distortion	O
and	O
denial	O
of	O
the	O
#climatecrisis.	O
Fox	B-COMPANY
News	I-COMPANY
,	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
,	O
The	O
Times	B-COMPANY
,	O
The	O
Sun	B-COMPANY
,	O
Sky	B-COMPANY
,	O
The	O
Australian	B-COMPANY
,	O
...	O
Few	O
carry	O
more	O
blame	O
for	O
our	O
current	O
predicament	O
.	O
https://t.co/hoLwmZppK1	O

#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
editorial	O
5	O
August	O
2019	O
:	O
"	O
Gun	B-OTHER
rights	I-OTHER
need	O
to	O
be	O
protected	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Second	O
Amendment	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
suicide	O
pact	O
.	O
"	O
https://t.co/A4WkiLknc4	O

I	O
just	O
read	O
two	O
articles	O
from	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
and	O
I	O
feel	O
soy	O
fucking	O
smart	O
!!	O
Like	O
,	O
current	O
events	O
?	O
YAS	O
I’m	O
in	O
that	O

Just	O
having	O
a	O
clear	O
out	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
drawing	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
4	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
year	I-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
old	I-OTHER
,	O
presumably	O
during	O
the	O
days	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
for	O
the	O
kids’	B-OTHER
page	I-OTHER
of	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
https://t.co/f1IoWgbM12	O

These	O
3	O
undated	O
videos	O
(	O
1	O
min.	O
22	O
secs	O
in	O
all	O
)	O
of	O
Nigerian	B-OTHER
soldiers	I-OTHER
battling	O
what	O
seem	O
like	O
Boko	B-OTHER
Haram	I-OTHER
terrorists	I-OTHER
with	O
old	O
,	O
barefly	O
functional	O
guns	O
tell	O
you	O
why	O
our	O
soldiers	O
are	O
sitting	O
ducks	O
for	O
BH	B-ORG
&amp;	O
why	O
they're	O
hurriedly	O
buried	O
in	O
mass	O
,	O
unmarked	O
graves	O
,	O
as	O
d	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/G3mkgcLtVI	O

"	O
Launching	O
a	O
Leadership	B-OTHER
Revolution	I-OTHER
"	O
-	O
NY	B-COMPANY
Times	I-COMPANY
,	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
and	O
USA	B-COMPANY
Today	I-COMPANY
best	O
seller	O
#leadership	O
https://t.co/mhFIp3SIH9	O

13	O
#Investing	O
books	O
to	O
read	O
this	O
summer	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
#FinancialEducation	O
https://t.co/bfsm1OsFhl	O
https://t.co/jK6l6sYbda	O

Take	O
an	O
early	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/8XerKar8Dm	O
https://t.co/FuOAXLynh5	O

This	O
article	O
appeared	O
today	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
Good	O
!	O
https://t.co/aO0pARhJvd	O

The	O
Defence	B-OTHER
Headquarters	I-OTHER
has	O
noted	O
with	O
dismay	O
an	O
Online	O
Article	O
by	O
“	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
”	O
purporting	O
that	O
the	O
Nigerian	B-ORG
Military	I-ORG
maintains	O
secret	O
graveyards	O
in	O
the	O
North	B-GEO-LOC
East	I-GEO-LOC
theatre	O
of	O
operation	O
.	O

#India	B-GEO-LOC
has	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
&amp;	O
humble	O
leader	O
.	O
#sushmaswaraj	B-PERSON
ji	O
was	O
called	O
India's	B-OTHER
'	O
best	B-OTHER
-	I-OTHER
loved	I-OTHER
politician	I-OTHER
'	O
by	O
the	O
US	B-OTHER
daily	I-OTHER
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
.	O
https://t.co/jr1yofB1KR	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/5CqQULMlUI	O

Dan	B-PERSON
Draper	I-PERSON
,	O
Managing	O
Director	O
of	O
@InvescoUS	B-COMPANY
,	O
recommends	O
The	O
Bitcoin	B-OTHER
Standard	I-OTHER
to	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	B-COMPANY
's	O
readers	O
.	O

https://t.co/tufVtocdCI	O

Hundreds	O
arrested	O
in	O
Moscow	B-GEO-LOC
as	O
protests	O
pile	O
pressure	O
on	O
Putin	B-PERSON
-	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/27EqbgQET8	O

thank	O
you	O
wall	B-COMPANY
street	I-COMPANY
journal	I-COMPANY
,	O
very	O
cool	O
!	O
https://t.co/NpjlwiRbSC	O

The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
:	O
Fox	B-COMPANY
Corp.	I-COMPANY
to	O
buy	O
majority	O
stake	O
in	O
Credible	B-COMPANY
Labs	I-COMPANY
for	O
$265	O
million	O
https://t.co/JZiksGx8Xs	O
#Business	O

https://t.co/2EOpJgAHUu	O
A	O
major	O
expose	O
about	O
the	O
#CFP	B-OTHER
Board	I-OTHER
of	I-OTHER
Standards	I-OTHER
was	O
published	O
in	O
the	O
#WallStreetJournal	B-COMPANY
this	O
week	O
.	O
J.R.	B-PERSON
Robinson	I-PERSON
of	O
Financial	B-COMPANY
Planning	I-COMPANY
Hawaii	I-COMPANY
helped	O
develop	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
Read	O
more	O
,	O
right	O
here	O
...	O

Is	O
Apple	B-COMPANY
losing	O
its	O
bite	O
?	O
Headwinds	O
for	O
iPhone	B-COMPANY
company	I-COMPANY
-	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
-	O
https://t.co/Ve9hcUIubi	O

“	O
Just	O
because	O
you	O
fail	O
doesn’t	O
mean	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
failure	O
.	O
It’s	O
just	O
a	O
situation	O
to	O
overcome	O
and	O
transform	O
.	O
”	O
Words	O
to	O
live	O
by	O
!	O
Share	O
the	O
positivity	O
of	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	B-COMPANY
best	O
seller	O
,	O
The	O
Coffee	B-OTHER
Bean	I-OTHER
and	O
learn	O
more	O
https://t.co/aERdzHxros	O
https://t.co/UBJPLtEv9U	O

So	O
the	O
Nigerian	B-ORG
Army	I-ORG
according	O
to	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
secretly	O
buried	O
about	O
1,000	O
soldiers	O
?	O
This	O
Boko	B-ORG
Haram	I-ORG
defeat	O
hen	O
.	O
Buhari	B-PERSON
is	O
the	O
greatest	O
scam	O
to	O
ever	O
plague	O
this	O
country	O
.	O
🤦‍♂️	O

Take	O
an	O
early	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
page	O
of	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
https://t.co/JwoiaYlNRV	O
https://t.co/jA5fLeQhsG	O

Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	B-COMPANY
Journal	B-COMPANY
editorial	O
board	O
issues	O
economic	O
warning	O
to	O
Trump	B-PERSON
over	O
his	O
new	O
China	B-GEO-LOC
tariffs	O

First	O
Shep	B-PERSON
Smith	I-PERSON
at	O
Fox	B-COMPANY
and	O
now	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
comes	O
out	O
against	O
@realDonaldTrump's	O
China	B-GEO-LOC
tariffs	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
utter	O
Trump	B-COMPANY
incompetence	O
https://t.co/Q3jleeulSq	O
https://t.co/pwI2n85OlV	O

⭐	O
#U.S.	B-GEO-LOC
Levies	O
New	O
Sanctions	O
Against	O
Russia	B-GEO-LOC
for	O
U.K.	B-OTHER
Spy	I-OTHER
Poisoning	I-OTHER
-	O
The	O
Wall	B-COMPANY
Street	I-COMPANY
Journal	I-COMPANY
⭐	O
https://t.co/YU2zVLvmpr	O